skinz.org 2015-03-08

# 

Skinz.org has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: **Cookies/Third Party Cookies**  
Please be aware that by using this website, any third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your user's browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on your website including but not limited to Google Adsense cookies. You can adjust these settings by going into your web browser and changing the cookies settings. In Internet Explorer this is under Tools, Internet Options, Privacy, Advanced and in Mozilla Firefox, it is located in Tools, Options, Privacy, Cookies.

**www.skinz.org** and network sites. The www.skinz.org site, and network Web sites ("sites") are operated by Skinz.org located in New York. You can reach us with questions regarding this statement via e-mail at [pro@prourl.com](mailto:pro@prourl.com). 

Your IP address is used only when you become a member as a backup identification tool for polls and other member services. 

Our sites use cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our sites, and for other purposes. These cookies are used soley for the sites, and the content contained is not distributed to third parties. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (name and e-mail address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information related to www.skinz.org only when requested by said user. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Your e-mail address will never be given or sold to a third party and will only be viewed by Skinz.org. Your pager e-mail address will not be disclosed and will only be used for sending breaking news upon request. Other information you use will only be used to collect broad demographic information about our visitors. 

This site contains links to other sites. **Skinz.org** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their e-mail address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). The customer's contact information is only used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving mailings they have signed up for; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected on our sites. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

**Public Forums**

Our sites make chat rooms, forums, and message boards, available free to users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our servers have strict security in place to prevent an intruder from retrieving personal information about our users. Staff overlook server access daily to ensure the above holds true. 

**Children's Guidelines**

This site gives children under the age of 18 the ability to publicly post or distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent. Please take proper measures if you do not wish your child to have access to public forums and message boards. As always, exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in a public forum. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [support@skinz.org](mailto:support@skinz.org)

**Correct/Update**

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

Email [support@skinz.org](mailto:support@skinz.org) to modify your surveys and user information. 

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, you can contact [pro@prourl.com](mailto:pro@prourl.com). For other questions regarding the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, contact [support@skinz.org](mailto:support@skinz.org). 

At SKINZ.ORG we are committed to providing you information tailored to your individual wants and needs. We also recognize the importance of protecting personally identifiable information relating to you, our users and subscribers. SKINZ.ORG does not collect personally identifying information about individuals, except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals. When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may request your name, street, and e-mail address to aid in our administration of the contest and to assist in contacting the winners.

SKINZ.ORG utilizes specialized "Server Software" to automatically collect information about which pages each user visits as well as the user's Internet Service Provider (e.g., aol.com). This information is used for internal review, to tailor information to individual visitors and for traffic audits. 

Under no circumstances will we give specific, identifiable information about our users to outside third parties. However, we will, from time to time, provide advertisers or potential advertisers with aggregated, anonymous information about our users. In addition, any personally identifiable information provided by subscribers as part of an advertiser promotion within www.SKINZ.ORG may be provided to such advertisers as needed for the reasonable administration of the promotion. 

At this time, SKINZ.ORG discourages the use of "cookies" throughout the Site. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can access and enjoy virtually all of the features of our Site. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve our ads on the Internet. These third-party advertising companies employ cookie and 1x1 pixel .gif technology to measure and improve the effectiveness of ads for their clients. To do so, these companies may use anonymous information about your visits to our Web site and other Web sites. This information can include: date/time of banner ad shown, the banner ad that was shown, their cookie, the IP address. This information can also be used for online preference marketing purposes. 

If you want to prevent a third-party advertiser from setting and/or reading cookies on your computer, currently you may either visit each ad network's web site individually and opt out or visit the NAI gateway opt-out site to opt-out of all network advertising cookies. Click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp) for the NAI gateway opt-out site. This site will also allow you to review the third-party advertising companies’ privacy policies. 

A user's personally identifiable information (e.g., name, e-mail address) may be required in certain instances. For example, if we run competitions or contests on the site, you may be required to provide information such as your telephone number and address in order to participate. The exact rules may vary in each case but the specific rules for any contest will state how that information may be used. We may also use personally identifiable information for marketing and promotional purposes. SKINZ.ORG may send you e-mail alerting you to new features, products, promotions, or services pertaining to our site as well as on behalf of our various sponsors. 

We do not control the privacy policies of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other sites to which we provide hyperlinks. Users should also be aware that, when you voluntarily disclose personal information in chat areas, bulletin boards, or other public forums, such information may be collected by others and may result in the receipt of unsolicited messages. 

Children: Be sure to ask your parents for permission before you send any information about yourself - like your name, address, or e-mail address - over the Internet, to us or to anyone else and before making any purchases online. 

Parents: We encourage you to get involved with your children's online usage and to be aware of the activities in which they are participating. Any personally identifiable information collected by SKINZ.ORG from children (that we are aware are children) will be used only for the internal use of SKINZ.ORG. Such use may include market research, prize verification, contest fulfillment or requests for information or materials, and may sometimes be included in our database. Such information will not be posted or published by us, or provided to any third parties, without your prior consent. Anonymous aggregated data is sometimes provided to other parties which we do business with, for statistical and market research purposes as described above. 

Finally you should be aware that if your child voluntarily discloses his or her name, e-mail address, etc. within various public forums (including bulletin boards and chat rooms), such disclosures may result in unsolicited messages from other parties. 

Technology on the Internet is developing at a fever pace. It is critical that SKINZ.ORG maintain its ability to rapidly adjust these policies in the future. By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by SKINZ.ORG. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

1/14/02 UPDATE: 

Third Party Advertising 

We use DoubleClick and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). 

Third Party Cookies 

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. 

8/20/02 UPDATE: 

Third Party Advertising 

We use MaxWorldwide and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). 

Third Party Cookies 

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. 

We welcome your questions and comments about our privacy policy. If you would like to drop us a line, please email pro@prourl.com.

**_****PICTURES, FILES and ARTWORK DISCLAIMER**** - UPDATED December 7 2005_**

All images contained on skinz.org, that are not original creations of skinz.org, are publicity photos, special permission grants and/or believed to be in the public domain. In the event that there is still a problem or error with 

Copyright ed material, the break of the Copyright is unintentional and noncommercial and the material will be removed immediately upon proof.

All images and content found on skinz.org are being used for entertainment, support and/or educational purposes only and fall into one or more of the following four categories:

1\. Original creations of skinz.org and are protected under U.S. 

Copyright law.

2\. Publicity Photos: Publicity items include graphics, logos, public relations photos, studio publicity photos, publicity sound clips, publicity movie clips, publicity videos etc., which were originally used for advertising/public relations purposes, and are being used to publicize and promote a celebrity, movie, television program, video, etc. 

3\. Special permission grants: In some cases special permission has been granted from the 

Copyright holder to use a specific image or images (credit is given when requested).

4\. Taken from sources believed to be in the public domain. These images, which are widely distributed for free use on various Internet web authoring sites, are freely available on the world wide web and have been compiled from various public media sources or have been submitted by users of the site through e-mail. We ask that images submitted to skinz.org by users are free of 

Copyright or are original images owned and/or created by the individuals submitting the image and, therefore, any image submitted to skinz.org is free of Copyright unless otherwise notified. Submission of original material, to skinz.org, explicitly implies permission of the further unrestricted use by skinz.org. It is assumed that all such images are indeed public domain, but since such images are passed around freely between sites, it is not always possible to trace them back to their original source. It is possible for Copyright ed material to inadvertently end up on public domain sites. In the event that there is still a problem or error with Copyright ed material, the break of the Copyright is unintentional and noncommercial and the material will be removed immediately upon proof. If you are the owner of material that appears on skinz.org please send proof to pro@prourl.com and the material will be removed promptly. However, if you are the owner and would rather credit be given for the material, instead of removal, we will gratefully give the appropriate credit desired.

skinz.org respects the intellectual property of others, and we ask our users to do the same.

skinz.org cannot and will not be held responsible for any legal consequences of images submitted by its users. 

skinz.org is a non-nudity site. 

Images or content of any kind being used and represented on skinz.org, in no way, suggest or imply the preferences, beliefs, affiliations, values, or morals of the people or persons being shown, viewed, or showcased. 

skinz.org is in no way affiliated with any of the celebrities on this site. 

All text, logos, symbols, and graphics (unless otherwise stated) are original 

Copyright ed creations of skinz.org and the use of these are not permitted without consent. All wallpapers on this site are free and intended solely for personal computer desktop use only. Usage of wallpapers and/or backgrounds on other websites is prohibited without prior consent. If you are unsure if you can use certain material, feel free to contact us at pro@prourl.com for permission.

DISCLAIMER OF LIABILITY:

skinz.org, nor any of its owners and/or employees shall be held liable for any improper or incorrect use of the information described and/or contained herein and assumes no responsibility for anyone's use of the information. 

DISCLAIMER FOR EXTERNAL LINKS:

The appearance of hyperlinks does not constitute endorsement by skinz.org of the linked web sites, or the information, products or services contained therein. skinz.org does not exercise any editorial control over the information you may find at these locations. skinz.org is not responsible for the contents of any off site pages referenced. The user specifically acknowledges that skinz.org is not liable for the defamatory, offensive, or illegal conduct of other users, links, or third parties and that the risk of injury from the foregoing rests entirely with the user.

If there is anything on skinz.org that you have a question about, please feel free to contact us at: pro@prourl.com.

* No hotlinking or bandwidth theft allowed!

†Please note that, due to security concerns, attachments cannot be accepted. Accordingly, any notification of infringement submitted electronically with an attachment will not be received or processed.

BY USING THIS WEBSITE YOU AGREE TO ALL OF THE ABOVE AND HOLD SKINZ>ORG OWNERS HARMLESS. 

Added April 1, 2009

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
